Then buckle up;
you're in for a cranky night.
(Amy:)According to the codicil
of the Relationship Agreement
(Amy:)which you insisted upon,
(Amy:)we're not allowed to pout
or be moody on date night.
(Sheldon:)You know I just put that in
because of uterus stuff.
(Amy:)Well, it applies to you, too.
(Sheldon:)I was afraid you might
bring this up,
(Sheldon:)so I have a work-around.
(Sheldon:)There you go.
(Sheldon:)As far as you're concerned,
I'm smiling.
(Sheldon:)Although, I must admit,
I'm smiling a little bit
(Sheldon:)at the moment because
this loophole is so brilliant.
(Raj:)So, Bernadette, have you thought
(Raj:)about how you're going
to redecorate this place?
(Bernadette:)You know, I'm thinking
(Bernadette:)ripping up the carpets,
(Bernadette:)maybe lose the wallpaper,
(Bernadette:)all new light fixtures...
(Raj:)You know,
if you knocked out this wall,